

CANDAN KIZILBOYA

- in linkedin.com/in/candankizilboya
- candankizilboya2@gmail.com
- **2** +36706712540

ABOUT ME

Energetic and passionate computer scientist with leadership, problem solving and communication skills & various past experiences ranging from management to programming.

Aiming to apply my past experiences and knowledge across different fields to benefit your company and further improve myself.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Flutter
- Python
- SQL
- C/C++/C#
- Linux/Unix
- Git
- Jira
- Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerBl, Word)
- Content Creation (Adobe & Inkspace)

WORK EXPERIENCE



Digital Project Manager Procter & Gamble - Budapest, HU

May 2023 - Present

- Successfully led cross-functional teams in the successful execution of digital initiatives, aligning project goals with company strategies to drive revenue growth and brand visibility.
- Efficiently managed project budgets, optimizing resource allocation and procurement to ensure on-time and on-budget project delivery, achieving cost savings.



Technical Communications, Trainee Nokia Solutions & Networks - Budapest, HU

April 2022 - May 2023

- Assisted technical experts on the creation of internal and customer documentation of complex products such as 3G, LTE and 5G mobile networks solutions.
- Gained information gathering skills and technical understanding of products, as well as expertise in technical content and graphics creation.



Yetkin Gencler, Trainee MEF University - Istanbul, TR

March 2020 - June 2020

 Participated in a 9-week traineeship program as a educational trainee. Gained knowledge and experience in various fields including; Python, information literacy, entrepreneurship, presentation techniques and Excel.

EDUCATION



BSc in Computer Science Eötvös Loránd University - Budapest, HU

September 2020 - July 2023



High School Diploma Vefa Lisesi - Istanbul, TR

September 2016 - June 2020



High School Diploma Quartz Hill High School - California, USA

August 2018 - June 2019

CERTIFICATIONS



Project Management Google Professional Certificates 2023



IoT Fundamentals: Big Data & Analytics Cisco Networking Academy

2022